Some families have secrets.
The Tank is a horror, thriller film directed by Scott Walker.
In 1978 Oregon, Ben and Jules inherit an abandoned coastal property
from Ben's late mother, who's never mentioned it.
The untouched house has been kept a secret for 40 years and
comes with a beautiful private cove and beach.
Jules searches for answers while Ben unwittingly
awakens a fiercely protective creature.
Jules, played by Luciane Buchanan.
Ben, played by Matt Whelan.
Jodie, played by Jaya Beach-Robertson.
Amos Tilbury, played by Mark Mitchinson.
Merial, played by Ascia Maybury.
Linda, played by Holly Shervey.
Tank Girl is a 1995 American post-apocalyptic science fiction film
directed by Rachel Talalay and written by Tedi Sarafian.
Based on the British comics series created by Jamie Hewlett and Alan Martin, the
film stars Lori Petty, Naomi Watts, Ice-T, and Malcolm McDowell.
Set in a drought ravaged Australia years after a catastrophic impact event, it follows the antihero Tank Girl (Petty) as she, Jet Girl (Watts),
and genetically modified supersoldiers called the Rippers fight Water & Power, an oppressive corporation led by Kesslee (McDowell).
After reading an issue of the Tank Girl comic she had received as a gift, Talalay obtained
permission from the comic's publisher Deadline to direct a film adaptation.
She selected Catherine Hardwicke to be the production designer, and worked
closely with Martin and Hewlett during the making of the film.
Tank Girl was filmed primarily in White Sands, New Mexico, and Tucson, Arizona.
The film's critically praised soundtrack was assembled by Courtney Love, and the
Rippers' makeup and prosthetics team was headed by Stan Winston.
Winston's studio were so enthusiastic about the project they cut
their usual prices in half to meet the film's budget.
Financially unsuccessful, Tank Girl recouped only about $6 million of its $25
million budget at the box office and received mixed reviews from critics.
Martin and Hewlett have since spoken negatively of their experiences creating the film, and Talalay
blamed some of the film's negative reception on studio edits over which she had no control.
Despite the box-office failure of the film, it has since become a cult
classic and has been noted for its feminist themes.
The tone is dark and intense.